[Music]
um okay so this is a fir side chat panel
discussion uh with uh with lauran and
Ashish um we're going to I'm going to
intro them uh in just a second actually
in fact all three of us three worked at
sneak um in fact asish has background
insecurity um having actually a ton of
ceso roles as well as being an amazing
presenter and host um of of a couple of
uh a couple of um podcasts uh most well
known for the cloud security podcast and
also started up a new AI cyber security
podcast uh lauran tal um has a super
strong engineering background although
it's in JavaScript and he's a lead in
the Seal team at sneak
um I worked with lauran for many many
years probably too many years maybe some
might say but it's an absolute pleasure
having you both on so
welcome pleasure to be here
man thank you for having me a JavaScript
person of course of course um I'm gonna
ask the first question And probably this
is going to be quite pointed at you laan
do llms write secure
code uh
no
well the real answer is sometimes not
all the time not very often depends so
basically no no okay is that is is when
we think about writing secure code and
security with AI we I guess we probably
think closer to the uh first party code
um is that the main risk the only risk
what do we what are we thinking are kind
of like the core things that developers
have to worry
about yeah that's an interesting uh way
to think about it because you could you
could kind of think of this as your
my first party code like my code is
basically your third party code because
maybe I'm like a maintainer of a of a
library and I built something and I used
AI to do that so it's my first party
code but then it becomes a component
that you actually use down the stream so
it's actually like all over the place
it's just code that uh could meet you in
very various places and from that aspect
it's it's basically you know it it it's
just like first part code but it's
really everything else yeah yeah and I
guess this kind of like leans into when
we think about infrastructure these days
asish um you know it's it's just code
right so is is this is
this from the cloud point of view I
guess we're talking about in exactly the
same voice right there's no there's no
differences or are there uh I guess I'm
one someone who keeps an optimistic view
um considering I've been talking about
AI C SEC for for some time now what I've
realized and I guess I I'm I guess I'm
partially in agreeance with Lon so I'll
probably add some context to this as
well I think um I talk about the example
and we talk about this qu of in the as
SEC podcast where it's like you know
when the car the self-driving car came
in first everyone like I'm gonna die
it's gonna be this is gonna be the most
horrible experience but someone quoted
an example which I I had not read of
until that point was like the number of
accidents that happened by humans far
outweigh the number of accidents
potentially could be prevented if
everything was self-driven now I'm not
saying we are there yet with code at the
moment but at the same time my viewpoint
is whether it's your Cloud code or your
JavaScript code or your Java code uh
irrespective I think we're definitely
closer than we were before to improve
the quality of the code we're producing
and I think that's kind of where as I
said I've got a very optimistic view not
because uh as a security person uh I
kind of have to find the silver lining
in the fact that I mean the new
technology is going to keep evolving and
we're going to create a space for
ourselves and all of us are here talking
about Ai and Native space as well what
that could mean for the future of
development as well are we going to be
like not I mean I guess I love uh I I
would I do want to do a shout out to the
podcast that you ran uh I think most
recent episode you guys did between
yourself guy and the conversation around
where this AI thing is going to go in
terms of whether uh we're going to think
about developing code using the
construct that we live in today and how
we develop code or are we going to focus
on and I I can't remember the exact part
but almost the way it was explained made
me think of Iron Man where you know how
Iron Man just go Jarvis can you just go
and do this kind of a thing it's like
you're you're you want you have an idea
you want to implement you want to
architect instead of trying to figure
out whe whether SQL injection is the
biggest problem you care about right now
think that's where I'm leaning more on
uh but hopefully kind of that g some
context K to hear what you guys think as
well yeah that that's really interesting
actually I got I've got two things to
follow up on that I guess one F first of
all when we think
about we think about what the code that
AI produces versus the code that we
produce are we are we um putting the bar
of what is acceptable code higher for AI
than we would ourselves and that that's
the kind of feeling I got when you were
talking about uh self-driving cars for
example it's okay for a human to have a
crash because that's that's human to do
that but when we when we when a when an
AI car crashes or an A driven car
crashes it's bad because because you
know we can blame the computer on that
we we can blame individuals who wrote
that code whatever it is are are we
setting that bar higher and I guess
luran maybe you should answer that as a
JavaScript
developer I like what you did there
Simon did you like that has nothing's
changed in six years has it r no nothing
it's just the
same um so first off yes I think we are
setting the bar the bar higher like if
we set it lower that would be kind of
pretty bad for us right like we kind
want to have it we we we want to have
code Drive everything right so we want
to have code not humans drive you know U
hard Bas spacers you know things like
that when to have you know code ride uh
the railways and not humans and stuff
like that so because you want to scale
that out because you kind of want to
automate the whole thing because you
want to throw code at everything right
so there's know infrastructure as code
you know security as code everything as
code and suddenly you know the world
becomes you know it itself kind of
defined by code because everything gets
kind of hyper productive replacement by
AI so yes of course you want the the bar
to set to be set High you want a very
low kind of error rate and and I think
that's that's the goal and we haven't
done we haven't been there yet and
really the whole breakthrough
Transformers and everything else that
kind of been happening in the last I
don't know like four five six years or
so uh uh in in kind of like in uh in
aggregate is it's kind of showing us
that this is where we want to go and I
think we want to be productive we want
to be able to uh run code fast but at
the same time it has to be secure it has
to be performant it has to comply with
specific regulations and policies that
we would want to see and and you know
kind no Branch outside that's that's
kind of like the goal that's what that's
what takes us from you know point a to d
without going through uh B and C and I
think that's that's where we should be
aiming for I was going to say is it the
nervousness that makes us keep a higher
standard for AI code like why are we
nervous about the fact that there is
more vulnerabilities being added are we
nervous about the fact that hey is it
going to do better than me like when the
first Uber Evolution kind of happened
when when before that we were all taught
going growing up never get into a
strangers card now we're like oh just go
all the way like as long as the number
matches don't really worry about
verification anything just get into any
car you see uh yeah but but like self
dri but like self-driving like cars had
like you know millions of millions of
like data points of like kilometers
driving or whatever like throughout
right that's that's what got them to be
like super good at what they
did of of human trained like it's it's
from Human yeah drivers so it's actually
picking up all those same errors
actually that follows up that follows
into my second question from from what
aish was kind of like saying he
mentioned kind of like I think you
mentioned code injection or something
like that when we think about the risks
are the risks the is it like an
exaggeration of existing risk so it's
just you know there's going to be more
code we're able to we're able to deliver
faster and so forth as a result is it
just that we're going to get an increase
the auto we're effectively in a more
autonomous way adding these types of
issues or are there other risks that you
know beyond the typical security
vulnerabilities that we should expect in
our code
oh sorry who was that for Leon or anyone
I think go I can go I have some opinions
on this as well because I think I I
probably lean on the whole we we
actually have seen this happen funny
enough uh whether it's your application
code infrastructure code when we went
down the automation path everyone who
was doing automation they wanted to do
the lowrisk activity being automated
first no one wanted to go automation
production that was never the case so I
imagine similar Evolution would happen
with code that is created whether
doesn't matter what kind of code it is
as it's created by AI agents as people
are or agentic AI as Gartner is calling
it now whatever uh the terminology you
know use or the kind of AI you might use
what you would find is at every point we
would as humans make a call for hey am I
okay for the quote unquote AI agent to
just take over this thing and I'm happy
with the fact that hey you know what
it's a backend function happens in the
middle of the night even if the service
goes down doesn't really matter
or we'll flip it around to say actually
you know what it's in the hospital I
don't want it to go and create anything
which is potentially life threatening I
I guess as as humans as much as one
would want to put money as the most
important thing at the end of the day uh
life is probably kept as a at a higher
level so I imagine when it comes to
things like your security compliance or
whe it comes to I guess the quality and
the Automation and the usage of AI would
be driven by more how uh where it's used
for automation similarly like low
activity task would be automatic it
would happen more frequently and
probably would happen even quicker like
I think there's a lot of use cases for
Security operation people already out
there we're already using for
documentation summarize Su summarization
and a lot of other things but where it
would make a difference and I think
where it would still remain slower and
probably the adoption would reduce quite
a bit and not because of nervousness it
just because of the criticality of what
that change could do in terms of a
health hospital Health Data like it's
not going to expose but hopefully
breaches reduced but it was not going to
expose my health data on the internet
hopefully but at least if it does some
human would want to check that before if
the change comes you are very optimistic
AES I did start by saying I'm a very
optimistic person because I I do want by
the way for people who are watching this
listening later I wanted to say that
security people are considered as
negative people I'm trying to change
that perspective that's kind of like my
aim so it's like as much as security
people think the Skynet is real I want
to change the perspective that I know
there's some there is some productivity
here AI is going to help improve our
productivity as well not just uh for the
business with your ceso hat on then
Ashish so talk even with those even with
those um Services which maybe aren't as
super critical um what would you do
differently compared to an existing
workflow whereby you have automated
tests and things like that knowing there
is AI uh generated code or even you know
with automated pushes and things like
that what would you do what would you do
differently in your workflow to defend
against potential uh whether it's errors
whether it's vulnerabilities and so
forth that are being injected at various
points uh I'll probably ask answer this
from the current point of time
perspective because I I still feel we
haven't reached that Pinnacle for code
uh so I'll probably answer based on what
it is today in terms of whether it's the
use of llms or use of uh AI or whether
it's use of productivity app I think the
primarily I would say the three areas
that you would find and for anyone who's
listening as well or watching this the
first one being me as a developer using
a quote unquote authorized co-pilot or a
third party co-pilot that's the number
one R people talk about I'm okay because
I have a Microsoft E5 license I want
people to use co-pilot but these days if
you just Google for co-pilot there's so
many co-pilots out there now you don't
know which one you're using so putting a
filter for co-pilot is probably not the
best approach to filter our third party
so anyone who may be using say a
co-pilot agent or coding agent from a
hugging face website or another website
that is open source that probably is the
number one risk a lot of people talk
about where yes we want to improve the
uh the code being created and code being
generated out but are we trusting the
right source to be creating the Cod
that's the first R most we will talk
about the second one we will talk about
is sorry no I just said I said yes I was
like nodding you agree as well um the
the second one I was going to talk about
was more around uh I think it's been
called the llm firewall but the idea
behind this is that it's a data coming
in and out so the data the data that you
are giving to your llm whether it's your
internal or external llm or the data
that you're getting back from it are you
trusting it in one go the ideal approach
over there people talk about is the fact
that you keep your llm model as dumb as
possible so that you just manage the
data security of what's going in and
what's coming out rather than thinking
about oh what's my llm security looks
like now the challenge with that is uh
and most organizations this is the way
they're approaching it they have a
wrapper or a proxy around chat gbd or
Claude which one of the two most popular
llm models very few people are creating
this at this point in time because it
just takes a lot of money to create your
own llm model the ones who are using
there they're probably using the CLA of
the openi version so the M file kind of
comes in where hey we have an agreement
with chat GPD we're using the Enterprise
version or the cloud Enterprise version
that's what we're going to use from API
call perspective so that's kind of where
that second space is the third one which
is probably the most boring one but
still relevant is the whole the third
party risk uh that we all talk about as
uh work people who work in cyber
security we have agreements with all the
third parties we work with whether it's
your Microsoft Amazon doesn't really
matter who you're working with
Salesforce uh anyone else or any other
third party you think of I definitely
find that the third bucket that's been
growing for a while is where we are
talking about third party between say if
something happens to the chat GPD data
although it's impossible for you to kind
of train your data by just dumping your
data into it because it requires a lot
more information than just me writing a
me uploading my uh my my current Place
slip into it suddenly it has my
sensitive information uh but that's the
kind of third risk hope but but it hope
May makes sense I mean I'm curious if
Lan or yourself have more risk that you
can probably talk about that maybe I me
and other seos all this thing can
actually learn from as well yeah I'm
thinking from like so like from the uh
if I put on the uh the coder hat again I
think from that perspective and this is
a this is a Yoda coder hat so what it
means is basically uh I think it runs
lates to a large kind of like blind spot
that exists for developers that's kind
of where I it so what it means is in
this is let's let's give let's give a
let's go back to like you know 10 years
ago or so maybe more when you know the
cloud started and you'd put like an
something on an S3 bucket like a file
that got uploaded so while you you you
thought that was like maybe secure you
know you did not save that file on dis
you did not have like bat reversal
vulnerabilities and things like that and
then you know the back end or the front
end team whoever uses you know the asset
would kind of like I think treat the
asset as secure right because it doesn't
come from user input it's it's on my S3
bucket right the file name is mine but
actually if that file name existed and
like had you know like a script tag in
it like an xss injection payload thing
then that would get saved as a string on
the bucket it wouldn't do anything to
like the AWS console but the moment you
trusted that and you took that and just
injected that to the Dom and just like
added that as like you know like a non
Puri you know non D purify now escaping
and nothing else done there output
encoding all L those things because you
trusted this is your data and not
something else that's the game over
right and I think it kind of exists with
with llms in the same way kind like he
used the llm but like you know promptu
injection we can of look at it from the
perspective
of having you know um what do I put it
like changing the the behavior of the
llm to do something else and most of the
time think people think about it like
you know like the Lera game right like
give me the password or do something
else order a new car do reserve a new
hotel at $1 for me all of those things
but at the same time if you use that llm
as a source for something like you use
that output in your database in
something else it might as well you
could prompt injector to actually
produce code that uh if you like do not
practice uh you know SQL query correctly
with like preper statements then you'd
get a tcal injection that's like you
know one example so I think what happens
is it creates more blind spots that we
did not know about before or did not
like pay too much attention to before
another example could be maybe like like
the training data so imagine like being
able to like poison things like you know
picle files and and uh and pytorch files
where you serialize some data maybe that
data that was serialized got into some
third party they were able to like
maliciously inject some payload into the
data it gets unserialized again and then
the model suddenly does something else
that it shouldn't have done before but
like as a developer you can like you
don't even think about this aspect of
like you know my training set my
training data my model my Tories all of
those kind of things and that's like a
whole blind spot that that exists as a
vulnerability as an attack vector and
you know suddenly because of llms you
kind of you know you you you use that
workflow but it it wasn't apparent
before that this was like a security
issue because all the data was something
that you trusted right it's was like you
know if you like to take a look at like
you know 15 years ago AI work machine
learning data it's stuff that you
ingested you know based on your internal
you know data scientist team and stuff
like that and you there would be some
guarantee that you know there's no Q
injections in there there wouldn't be
some undesired behaviors in there yeah
and and I think a lot of this when we
think about trading data and there are
absolutely attacks and threat threat
vors when we talk about data poisoning
and things like that but of course
training data is not perfect anywh and
when we think about the difference
between source code and infrastructure
as code is a good example we had um
Arman dadgar on the on the podcast and
there were some really interesting
thoughts which kind of like maybe really
Ponder the differences between training
data from an IAC point of view to to a s
a first party code uh source code point
of view and that what people will
typically put on open- Source repos uh
there there are going to be different
levels of what people try to try to put
on for example if I was to if I was to
have an llm train on a ton of my open
source Java code JavaScript code
whatever it is there there's going to be
good examples there of how I might want
to do something whether it's in an
Enterprise way or non-enterprise way
however when we think about
infrastructure as
code the
I I think there's a different level of
acceptance as to about as to you know
whether an Enterprise level um IAC file
is going to be up loading into an open
source repo or not for example you know
if there are and this was one of the
examples that Armon gave if there are
way more public buckets in the world and
of course from the from the Enterprise
side you would expect okay there will be
a few but not many when there are way
more public buckets in the world if I
ask for a um for for an S3 bucket the
llm is most going to give me a public
bucket right but that's not from my
point of view what I actually want as my
default because it's it's insecure by
default there um so does this mean that
first of all every AI generated IAC if I
ask for for an S3 bucket is going to
come back to me as as as as public and I
guess the bigger question is is the
training data for IAC just not relevant
as much to to to an
Enterprise uh need and is there anything
we can kind of do about that
aish this is way of the data that you I
think uh but it's a good point though
because I would question so most of the
Enterprises that I've been talking to
who are trying to build llm or chat BS
or whatever the use case for themselves
is I think a lot of them are using their
existing internal data to build their LM
models now to your point I mean the
whole context or or the premise of where
we started was that we as humans are
already producing bad quality code so
like they probably turn training on bad
quality code and bad quality
infrastructures code as well there's
there's a multitudes of challenges uh
that we already facing in our day-to-day
jobs as developers as Architects or
security people as well so perhaps to to
your point I would flip that analogy to
more how reliable is your internal data
that you're using to train your model uh
yeah I mean 100% I would love for it to
do the right thing but does anyone have
the time to go through their internal
data whether it's or unstructured for do
they trust the quality of it I mean but
then if we do not and we go outside and
to your point look at the data that's
being somehow produced by llm agent that
helps me build amazing quality code but
all I what I did not realize is behind
the scene it was using all the public S3
buckets and that's what it gave me I
think it would be a balancing act at
that point in time but I truly believe
uh where we sit at this point in time
and I think the way
most of these llm agents are going a lot
of them have gone down the path of
having an Enterprise license and having
a private so even in uh Microsoft Azure
you can have a completely private llm
does not talk to the internet you're
still looking inside so I I imagine
there's bit of time required before it
gets to a point where people are
comfortable but their train data is
always going to be the problem like I
think as much as all of us are excited
and want to jump onto the bandwagon yes
I want to do AI but you realize Ashish
who was there six years ago like left
basically a bag of rotten potatoes uh
just lying around and never even
bothered naming it there was no tags on
it there's no like this is part of the
area that no one touches no one talks
about and now suddenly llm wants a wants
a piece of it that would make many
people nervous so I I I feel like
there's a there's a journey to be had
over here and I I would see we're still
in the starting phase I think that hope
that makes sense because I kind of feel
like there two parts to it but also we
are still in the beginning stages
yeah no that makes sense and I think one
of the other The Next Step I guess there
once we when we think about um when we
think about not just finding issues um
or or refining what what the llms put
out is actually is actually making
suggestions to fix um and in that point
I guess you know the LM is just as
capable of of you know suggesting fixes
first first time around versus
identifying issues and then creating
fixes around them um what are the risks
in relying upon those fixes to or
suggested fixes to to my code I guess
we're talking about security here today
we just had a performance session uh
last last time around um it's it's going
to it's going to apply to a ton of
different areas but specifically and Lan
I think you're probably well placed here
from the first party code point of view
yes AI can suggest fixes what are the
risks so I would say it's against
suggest fixes but the fixers will be
suggested based on some you know
statistical model out of whatever it got
trained on and whatever context it
thinks it has but it doesn't really has
the right context and I think that is
key so like there's so much that is
going on within like you know when you
go beyond like The Benchmark You Know
sample repository that you compare you
know various Tools around and code and
like the to-do apps that you build with
with AI once you go deep down enough and
things get complicated I think at that
point there's a ton of context that is
needed and understanding of code flow so
I will give you one example that I think
makes total sense where llms would
actually try to fix something but would
actually get you get you hacked so
imagine that you are on a piece of code
in a in in your file and you are working
with URLs and you are you know you you
you practice something that's maybe like
you know URL and coding or like you like
ask the like the result of the AI is
giving you some code that relates to
that and you you ask it to like secure
it right and it says okay let's do URL
encoding or the other way around let's
do URL decoding whatever like the
depends on like the current process
let's say let's say that this is what it
suggests and by the way that's that's
probably one of the things it should do
so like that's a proper process but what
happens when it is not aware that
somewhere up the chain right some in
some you know let's say this is your you
know service and in some other service
you interact with or you know the route
the controller whatever you know the the
archit is you actually already did a URL
encoding so now you have double URL
encoding and that is potentially like a
security vulnerability like waiting to
happen due to the double encoding and so
if the llm doesn't know to like trace
your code pads and say well well you
actually did an encoding before you
should not really reapply the encoding
because you could suffer the double
encoding injection then that's going to
get you busted and so that's why it
needs more than being just a statistic
model and sometimes like vulnerabilities
in most of the cases honestly are very
nuanced and very complicated while it's
sometimes easy to just you know
demonstrate some code injection some
cross side scripting that we show in a
vulnerability and you know there it is
it's it's usually most of the time
vulnerabilities are chained together
they are more complicated people you
know chain one to another like a
prototype pollution to do code injection
to do command injection to open a shell
there's like a a layered approach when
things happen in the real world rather
than what we kind of you know demo so
having that nuance and
understanding is is I don't think that
kind of fits the statistical model and
maybe those things maybe those llms and
AI agents and the whole you know geni
you know General way of coding get
smarter where it will be able to then
kind of like Infuse several learnings
and several paradigms together like both
the model but also some applied you know
uh logic and something else that would
be great but like at this point in time
it's just super basic and it's as if it
kind of saved you the time to like
Google how to properly do you know path
validation versus just asking the llm
it's not at that point where you would
ask it to fix it and you could count on
it yeah yeah yeah very interesting we
got a minute or so till Qui Q&A um let's
let's invite the audience to also ask
some questions um while the audience is
thinking of questions and pinging them
into the chat I'd be interested in just
asking more of a cultural question and I
think when we think about uh you know
devop changes over over the last 10 20
years or so we've seen platform teams
we've seen this this amazing devops
engineer role been created um I I
personally see there's a place on that
platform team for maybe certain security
engineers and and people who do work
closely with with the developers the
paved Road style approach when we so
first of all may maybe it'd be
interesting to hear your thought on that
but beyond that do do do we see from an
organizational change point of view an
AI security paved Road or anything like
that also sitting in the in the um in in
the platform team I'd I'd love to know
how you think that the teams are going
to change aish why don't you lead us
with this uh I think the the so there is
already I guess many companies have
already started working on AI projects
and the way they're dealing with this at
this point in time is the platform
Engineers themselves are the ones who
are because from a workload perspective
if you look at the components that get
used for building an AI application
those really haven't changed I guess you
still use cuties as your foundation
there you still have databases so all
that layer hasn't really changed so
though those people would still continue
to work on it I think the only the only
point you would see Evolution like that
when the number of AI applications
outweigh the number of regular
applications you have so it kind of
happened to your point example where we
started with devops we had Cloud became
Cloud security engineers Cloud security
This Cloud security that then kubernetes
became popular then oh let's just do
kubernetes security engineer I think it
just comes down to if we ever get to a
point where the number of applications
which are Aid driven in your
organization are more than the regular
non- Aid driven or by then they are
quote unquote Legacy application then
yeah maybe uh we'll see that but maybe
not right now I guess kind of where I'm
coming
from yeah any thoughts
lean yeah I I agree I think it's a bit
early to call like an AI security
engineer I think it's definitely not
early to have like AI engineering thems
just because that's like
very like that's like like ai ai is here
right like llms are here they're like
you know Among Us um sometimes they they
present themselves as Java llms which
you shouldn't trust uh but you know they
are among us and I think AI engineering
is like is is something that that should
probably exist I think AI security
engineering is is a bit de down it's
it's indeed like I don't know if there's
like kubernetes security Engineers it's
like very very very specific you kind of
like I think like depend on the tooling
the ecosystem you know the
foundation um to like run a bunch of
like you know the security
responsibility to an extent you can like
Outsource the risk because it's a third
party and things like that um and I I I
somewhat feel like AES that it's kind of
early to understand what it is since we
don't exactly know like even how to
secure it properly so U it's we'll see
Yeah question coming in from the
audience uh Min asks it's interesting
that open source code used to be seen as
more secure than proprietary code
because open source projects are
transparent about potential
vulnerabilities um I gather from what
you are saying now is that no is that no
longer the case when it comes to models
and agents did I understand this
correctly I think it's still the case
though I think it's still the case that
both open source and propriety data
cannot be trusted that's where the I
mean I guess of the whole foundation of
the nervousness that we all have is that
no matter which way you face if you look
at internally uh there was the aish
example that I went for who left left a
bag of Rotten Tomatoes ages ago that is
still hanging around there are parts of
the organization that we still don't
touch or talk about that is it so that
is never going away it's still going to
be there if you look at open source uh I
think I'll go back to the episode
example that you gave Simon earlier uh
where Arman kind of spoke about the
levels of like I did my first GitHub
repository back when I was trying to
understand what what is it like what is
it to code something and my that my that
repository is still there to the point
that today when I'm teaching people
cities and cloud and all of that I have
the mature repository as well I mean the
same Ashish has two repositories which
are complete different experiences I've
never touched the the first one again
because I'm just toass to talk about it
now that I did it publicly but still uh
I think that's where I find that I would
say there's untrust or nervousness on
both sides I I wouldn't say one is
better than the other yeah or more
secure I would take I think it's more
nuanced and it's it's really hard to
compare open source code like like
comparing third party V uh third party
dependencies with like uh third party
models if you if you if that's what kind
want to compare it's super hard because
the I think the foundation is very
different so for example to to review
and scan like get an audit of an open-
Source thirdparty package I could I
could see the maintainers I could see
who contributed I could see a git log of
all the code added how it was added when
fixes were made right like in the code
in the releases I can see what third
party it use uses to do things um I can
have like you know provan at the station
at like the signature level of how how
versions were published I don't really
have that level of data at the model
right like I can't see ex I cannot see
like how exactly was it trained uh I I I
am BBE being told how but I don't know
how it was actually I don't think like
the same uh the same standards of how
you do codee to how you train models
exist yet and I think that's like the
the Nuance that kind of kind of escapes
and it's it's kind of easy to maybe
Overlook but I think that's that's an
important aspect when you need to audit
you know code versus versus a model
yeah we're pretty much out of time but I
want to add this last question because I
feel like it's a really great question
from Macy here what about social
engineering risks uh when teams
leveraging um generative AI what steps
can be taken um what steps can teams
take against this or is it too early do
we not know what those are just yet I
would say there's definitely some and I
guess there are different ways to take
the social engineering aspect the one
that comes to mind with geni is the fact
that I work as a developer and I want to
know what's the salary of Ashish Aisa
because I'm just curious he seems to be
quite Fancy on the internet I wonder
where he gets all the money from so so I
the the way people are talking about
this at the moment is that there needs
to be almost like a quote unquote data
access manager for a lack better word uh
the the way people are doing this is how
do you manage access for different
identities based on their roles that is
one aspect for social engineering I I
would argue this could be done better in
the AI world because you have a lot more
sense you have a lot more understanding
of where your data is what kind of data
it is and who can access it and what
they should be doing it's not just a
policy document it's actually
implemented I think that's where I feel
they'll be really interesting but in
some aspects really early because we
haven't really seen AI based attacks at
scale so we don't really know what
social engineering could be like as well
so maybe in that aspect maybe too early
cool I'm being shoved off shave shoved
off stage here because we have another
session starting in just a few minutes
um so first of all a massive thank you
to both Ashish and luran it's an
absolutely pleasure to have you on the
IR native Dev likewise thank you thanks
for having us